ebooktake.biz 2013-10-05

# Terms And Privacy - Free Ebook Download

Federal law requires that I notify you of my privacy policy. My clients expect their confidential information to be treated with the utmost discretion. I take this responsibility seriously. All information given to me in confidence remains confidential.

Customer information: The information you provide is needed so that I can make appropriate insurance and other recommendations. Some of this information is known as nonpublic personal information. I have no need to seek or collect nonpublic personal information from third party sources, since my clients provide this information directly. I strive to maintain accurate, up-to-date records in order to serve my clients. Any inaccuracies that are called to my attention are corrected promptly.

Sharing information: I do not share nonpublic personal information with any outside persons or organizations. However, I cannot rule out the possibility that, at some future date we may need to contract with a third party source of administrative or technical support. In such case, I will require the third party to agree to safeguard such nonpublic information and to use it only for the agreed purpose. I do not sell, rent, or loan my client list to any third party. I do not give prospective clients the names of existing clients unless the client has authorized me to do so.

Access to and protection of information: Only those governmental agencies with a valid reason for doing so have access to my files containing nonpublic personal information. I maintain security standards to protect nonpublic personal information.

Disclosure of privacy policy: I provide this privacy notice for informational purposes and I will update it as required by law. If you have any comments, suggestions or questions about my privacy policy, please let me know.

### Personally Identifiable Information

Ebooktake never collect your personally identifiable information except the email address when you register as a user of Ebooktake.

### Sharing Information.

Ebooktake may share certain information regarding our customers and former customers among Ebooktake affiliates only in accordance with our strict security standards and confidentiality policies, and applicable laws. We hold our employees and agents fully accountable for adhering to these standards, policies and laws.

From time to time opportunities arise that we believe will benefit our customers and former customers. On a selective basis, we may share your name, address, telephone number and email address with third parties, such as insurance agencies, home warranty companies and tax service providers, record storage companies, moving companies, and other businesses that provide services to home owners, to market financial and non-financial products and services that may interest you. We will only provide this information to companies making these offers available to you under strict confidentiality agreements. For instance, we may share certain information with our strategic business partners with whom we have agreements to help provide customers with Ebooktake One Stop Shopping Services, or with other companies which help us to conduct business, such as credit bureaus and businesses which provide account maintenance, analysis and servicing. We may also provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law. If you do not want to participate in these opportunities, please refer to the Opt-Out Notice Section below to learn about how to opt out.

### Usage tracking; Collection of your IP Address.

Your IP address is a unique number used to identify your specific computer on a public network. Ebooktake may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, such as diagnosing problems with our server, to analyze consumer behavior and trends, and to audit the use of our site. IP addresses are not used to personally identify a customer and are kept anonymous. Ebooktake may use IP addresses to identify a customer when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site terms of use or terms of service, or to protect our service, site's, customers or others.

### Use Of Cookies.

Ebooktake may use "cookies" to track web site visitors. Cookies are small amounts of data that the visitor retains on their computer, which enables the visitor to go back to saved information from a previous visit. They are also used to tailor the navigation of the web site to be consistent with the visitor's preferences and to enable them to see their sales agent's contact information in some cases as they work their way through the web site.

### Links to Other Web Sites.

Please be aware that when you click on links that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to their respective privacy policy. While Ebooktake supports the protection of privacy on the Internet, Ebooktake cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any web site.

### Legal Disclosure.

Ebooktake may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Ebooktake's terms of use or terms of service, or may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with any of Ebooktake's rights or property, other Ebooktake customers, or anyone else Ebooktake may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.
